Shattano, Shattano, Shll,
Chess, Chess, Hazz, Chess,
Thank you.
Let's go.
Oh, my God.
Are you not feeling
well, Mr. Joe Starr? Yes.
Thank you for asking, Avdol.
I've had some bad experiences
with planes in the past.
As I mentioned before,
we have but 50 days to confront Dio,
if we have not succeeded by then.
Yes, I understand.
If we cannot make it in
time, then Holly could die.
What?
What was that?
Jostar-san, the engine on the
left side has caught fire.
Calm down.
Everyone remain seated.
But Jostar-san, the engine...
Don't worry.
I'll go ask the pilots about this myself.
Captain, please tell me
what's happening here.
I'm trying to find out.
We're rapidly losing altitude.
We're out of control.
You have to return to your seat.
Unless we regain control, we're
going to crash into the ocean.
What did you say?
What a pain.
The important thing is
that everyone is all right.
Many ships travel through these waters.
They'll pick up our distress signal
and surely come to our rescue.
I sure hope you're right about that.
We certainly can't afford to hang
around in a place like this for long.
But I wonder, could our enemies
have caused this accident?
Huh?
Hmm, my friends, it seems that
our luck has not run out just yet.
Huh?
Please signal them.
Right then, now we can go back.
Guess we shouldn't take my natural
good luck too lightly, huh?
Is something bothering you, Avdolsan?
The ramp has already been lowered for us,
but why aren't any of the crew
members showing themselves?
No one's coming to meet us.
Just where the hell is the crew, anyway?
Just like that famous abandoned
ship, the Mary Celeste.
Hey!
Is there anyone here?
Anyone here?
He's here! He's here!
He's here!
In any case, let's investigate the ship.
Is something wrong?
Look at this window.
How could they have spotted us
through a window as filthy as that?
It appears there is no one
in the engine room either.
So there's no one on board
what was that just now?
Josa what is it there
was a sound from inside!
What a gigantic monkey.
This appears to be an orangutan.
Is he telling us to open the cage?
Certainly looks like it to me.
Oh, you're a pretty
smart guy for a monkey.
Please be careful.
An orangutan is five times
stronger than a human,
so he could easily rip your arm off.
He's not starving,
which means there's at least one
person on board who's been feeding him.
Right, then.
Let's go find the owner.
Hmm?
What the?
Hmm, look up there, on the bridge.
Hmm?
This is a ghost ship. Ridiculous.
I think it would be best
if we all stay together.
What do you think?
Anyone?
This ship is too dangerous.
What can we do now in
the middle of the ocean?
But we're not sure where
the ship is headed yet.
What's that?
I guess we'll have to go see.
Hmm.
Bonjour, Monsieur Joestar.
Greetings to your party.
Ah, you! Wait.
Tell me, how is it you know about us?
A man with a birthmark
shaped like this told me.
You're one of them.
Justice! Look out!
What?
My Stan's name is Silver Chariot.
So, Avdol, it would appear that
you are very anxious to die.
I made a clock out of fire on that table.
Before it burns 12 o
'clock, I will kill you.
That was very formidable swordplay.
I am truly in awe.
But you say you would
kill me by 12 o 'clock.
Well,
don't you think that you are being just
a little bit too vain, man from France?
My greeting is overdue.
Please allow me to introduce myself.
My name is Polnareff,
Jean-Pierre Polnareff.
Merci beaucoup.
My sincere thanks for your introduction.
Now that...
All Avdol's stand did was move its arm,
and the lower half of the
table has burned away.
It is very important that you realize my
stand's fire is not like
some ordinary flame.
And because my stand can control fire
at will, it is called Magician's Red.
Hmm. Impressive.
But a while ago, you said I was too vain.
You think I'm vain about
my swordplay skill?
Too vain, you said?
Can you still say that now?
Amazing.
He was able to pierce five
coins with a single thrust.
No, there's more to it than that.
Take another look at those coins.
I see what you mean.
Very good, so you understand
what this means then.
My stand can cut, parry and block
your fire with complete control.
In other words, my friend, this means
you are virtually powerless against me.
When did he...?
Avdol, I could kill you here and now,
but the size of this room
put you at a disadvantage.
A more open space would allow you to
use your ability at full power, right?
Beating you there would be a more
suitable victory for my stand.
Everyone, get in line.
One by one, I will cut each of you apart.
Well, Avdol, Mr.
Joestar, please do not
interfere with this.
Just as he said, with this much open
space, I can more freely use my stand.
I will predict your destiny.
I predict that you will destroy
yourself with your own stance abilities.
What happened to your vaunted flame?
If you're not going to
breathe fire, then I'll start.
That man certainly got a
lot of bloody nerve while he
was just waiting for
Magician's Red to breathe fire.
You don't stand a chance against me.
He's coming for real this time.
By Jove, I wouldn't want to get
broiled by this next attack.
Crossfire coming here!
Hey!
Is that really all the power you've got?
If so...
The stand's flame was too powerful.
It's burning Avdol instead.
Just as I said, right, Monsieur Avdol?
Ah, what a desperate struggle, eh?
What is this resistance?
Once again, now, let's fire!
His stand is melting.
He's badly burned.
He's lucky he's only severely injured.
No, perhaps I should say he's unlucky.
In any case, he won't be able
to get up for three months.
His stand has been reduced to
a pulp and is unable to fight.
Well, Mr.
Joestar, we should start talking about
the best way to get to Egypt from here.
Look up there!
What?
I can't believe it.
Bravo!
Why is his body floating there in midair?
Look carefully through
the eyes of your stands.
His stand.
Allow me to present Silver Chariot
without his protective armor.
Well, you look appropriately amazed.
If you don't mind, please explain
to me how this is possible. Good.
Your attitude is most commendable.
The explosion earlier was not
my stand being blown to bits,
but the impact of my stand
throwing off his armor.
Only his armor was burned by your fire,
so I was able to get by
with only minor injuries.
And now, with the armor
gone, I can move much faster.
So you're saying that
the weight of your armor
prevented you from avoiding
my crossfire hurricane?
Oui, that is correct.
Which means that without
your protective armor,
you would not survive being
struck by another CFH.
Oui, but that is impossible. Impossible?
Why?
Because I'm about to show you
something that will horrify you.
What the it can't be a person should only
have one stand hmm you
appear to be horrified?
These after images affect not just your
sight but your other senses as well.
How about this sword play now!
That was an after image your stunts
are useless against my stand now!
Avdol!
You should know that I developed a
variation on my crossfire hurricane attack.
The unkshake fire is
normally a single flame,
but I can break it up and hurl
it as many separate flames.
Now really, Avdol!
Not good.
His stands have formed a defensive circle.
He'll strike the flames
back, just like before.
Easy, easy, easy, easy!
I will strike them back.
What the...
That is the hole Polnareff's stand made
earlier when he struck back Avdol's flames.
I get it now.
He made use of a hole created
in the midst of battle.
His ability to split the
flame made it possible
for him to pull off this clever strategy.
Burning to death would be
a very painful way to die.
Use that blade and put
an end to your misery.
I was so vain, thinking my swordplay
would never be beaten by mere flames.
For that, I choose to
burn to death gracefully.
Consider this to be a
salute to your abilities
from the one who you defeated in battle.
His proud spirit goes beyond Dio's orders.
This man who remains true to the code
of honor that you call chivalry. Right.
If we let him die like this,
we may regret it later.
Perhaps there's a very good reason why
this man became one of Dio's assassins.
We're safe now.
Our enemy has been defeated.
I have to admit, you really
had me worried for a while.
What a relief.
Hey, watch out!
Hit the deck!
Damn, Ape is a stand user.
He turned that bolt into a pipe. Jotaro!
Chotaro!
This entire ship is his...
His stand!
Hey, monkey.
Your hairy ass is next.
Jotaro!
It seems to be over now.
But whether this boat will break down
or reach land, Is anyone's guess.
Who would have imagined his stand
made use of a little boat like this?
If we'd known this would happen, maybe
we would have tried to tame that monkey.
He's really something to have recovered
from those injuries so quickly.
There must be something important he
feels he must accomplish in this life.
Otherwise, no matter how young he is, he
would not have been able to heal this fast.
Mr.
Joestar, I may be prying, but I have
noticed that you're always wearing gloves.
Please don't tell me that your
left hand is actually a right hand.
My left hand a right hand?
That is a very peculiar question to ask.
For a long time, I've been searching for
a man whose hands are both right hands.
This is an honorable wound I
received in battle 50 years ago.
My apologies.
Please forgive me.
Polnareff, would you kindly
tell us what this is all about?
I've been looking for the man who
brutally murdered my younger sister.
It happened three years ago.
That day my sister was walking
home from school with a classmate
I don't know his face, but his
hands are both right hands.
Obviously, someone
possessing a stand ability.
I made a vow that he would pay for all the
things he did to my younger
sister with his life.
Then, one year ago, I met Dio.
But, who are you?
I can see a man, boldly
confronting you in your mind.
Listen, how about you
and I become friends?
If you will help me with my
work, I will lend you a hand.
Perhaps I can find that man for you.
So, I was ordered to kill you all,
and even though I knew it
was a whisper from the devil,
I'd made a deal to get the information
I needed to avenge my sisters.
death.
He's very good at finding and taking
advantage of people's weaknesses.
And according to the
story he just told us,
Dio already knew the identity of
the man who killed his sister.
What?
Polnareff, what are you going to do now?
I'd like to join you guys
on your mission to find Dio.
If I go after him too, I might
meet the man who killed my sister.
A jolly good idea.
Our goals may be different, but
our destination is the same.
All right, then.
Let's stop messing around
and get our butts to Egypt.
This is going to be a blast.
Oh, those Egyptian women are so mysterious
and appealing that I can hardly wait.
I thought he was a man who lived
by a code of honor and chivalry,
but now I'm not so sure.
His mood certainly changes in a hurry.
His mind and his instincts seem
to be completely independent.
Oh, what a pain.
Strength.
So useless.
Not only that, even the chariot
Polnareff double-crossed us.
However, all the cards of
destiny still remain in my hands.
Don't allow this to trouble you, Lord Dio.
No matter how many of those
useless worms defect to the enemy,
they can never be a match for your power.
Besides that, the Emperor and the Hanged
Man are already on their way to India.
One of them will do it.
The Hanged Man's right hands
will take care of them for sure.
Because the Master of
the Invincible Stand,
the Hanged Man, he is
my precious dearest son.
His name is J. Gaia!
Let's go.